[{"answer": "Well, they're going to have a lot of questions.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What do they need to say in order to justify and try to convince hesitant colleagues that this is the right thing to launch military strikes against targets in Syria?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, I've said from day one as a result of what has happened that I would.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Based on all of our previous conversations, everything I've heard, Senator Corker, you're on board right now with the President, you're inclined to vote yea if the resolution were right now?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Wolf, I was in the region two and a half weeks ago and I was totally embarrassed and dismayed that not a single shipment of arms has yet made its way in the vetted opposition.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Is that the answer you've been getting?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "You know, Wolf, I don't know what's going to happen in either body.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What should the President do then?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, let's be clear.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Why do you believe it's necessary now?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, I feel confident that our colleagues, my colleagues both on the Republican side of the aisle as well as the Democratic side of the aisle are not going to jeopardize the credibility of the United States.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "What if he gets rejected there as David Cameron did in Britain?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Oh, there are other countries.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Why can't other countries do it?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Look, that's honestly something, Wolf I'm not of liberty to say.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Which countries will use their military power to attack targets inside Syria?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "And that's going to be important.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Militarily?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Are you saying militarily?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "In both military and diplomatic and political support, there are dozens of nations who had committed to back us up.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Not just politically or vocally but militarily they will support the United States, they will go in with their F-16s, their own missiles, their firepower, and target sites in Syria?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, of course I have great respect for my colleague, Debbie Wasserman Schultz, and she's been doing this a lot longer than I have.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Congressman, why do you disagree so strongly with Debbie Wasserman Schultz's and with the President?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "What language that I read in the classified documents and what I heard was highly confident.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "But do you believe that the intelligence that the Obama Administration has presented to you in classified briefings that it is 100 percent certain that the regime of Bashar al-Assad used sarin gas, poisoned gas to kill all those civilians?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "That was President Obama this week and I'm Wolf Blitzer and for Piers Morgan.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What message will we send if a dictator can gas hundreds of children to death in plain sight and pay no price?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, no, it is a political gamble.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "He will get the House of Representatives to authorize the use of military force?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I command them for going this route because it think it portends for the future.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Should the President have gone through this legislative route or should he have just done it without Congressional Law authorization?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I think the risk of that is relatively low.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Are you afraid that even a limited strike could drag the United States into a prolonged conflict inside that Syrian civil war?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "You know, we can't be sure of that but what we can be sure of is they don't seem to plot it out what would happen if that red line was crossed.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Was he speaking carelessly or was he speaking thoughtfully?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Yes, I tend to think it would be.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Would it be catastrophic?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "You know, I think that it actually had might.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "If this is a really relatively modest Tomahawk cruise -- cruise missile strike for two or three days, will that accomplish much in the bigger picture of the civil war in Syria?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I very much doubt it.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Do you think -- you were just in Turkey, we saw your show yesterday, do you think the Turkish regime, the Turkish government would use military equipment, their NATO ally to bomb targets in Syria?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I think you can make him pay a price for sure.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Do you think it's possible?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Do you want to make a final point?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "It is, but that doesn't mean the next president's not going to have a Grenada, or Panama, or Libya, or some sort of intervention where they bypass Congress.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Yes, you agree Doug Brinkley that this politically, historically speaking is a huge, huge moment in presidential history?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so because it's all about the chemistry and the atmospherics of the moment.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Would executive authority be undermined down the road?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "HAPIRO: I think he will have the votes at the end of the day.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Will he have the votes in the Senate and the House?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "One of two -- the number of people who will say to the leadership, \"I'm with you, if you absolutely need me.", "docId": "130902pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "It's going to be -- I mean you think it's going to just win by one or two votes?", "qSentId": 459}]